Discover the first special forces mission in history.
The Ministry of Ungentlemanly Warfare is a action,
comedy, war film directed by Guy Ritchie.
During World War II, the British Army assigns a group of competent soldiers to
carry out a mission against the Nazi forces behind enemy lines...
A true story about a secret British WWII organization
— the Special Operations Executive.
Founded by Winston Churchill, their irregular warfare against the Germans helped to
change the course of the war, and gave birth to modern black operations.
Gus March-Phillips, played by Henry Cavill.
Marjorie Stewart, played by Eiza González.
Anders Lassen, played by Alan Ritchson.
Freddy Alvarez, played by Henry Golding.
Brigadier Gubbins 'M', played by Cary Elwes.
Geoffrey Appleyard, played by Alex Pettyfer.
The Ministry of Ungentlemanly Warfare is a 2024 historical war comedy film directed, co-written and produced by Guy
Ritchie, and starring Henry Cavill, Eiza González, Alan Ritchson, Henry Golding and Alex Pettyfer.
Based on the 2014 book Churchill's Secret Warriors: The Explosive True Story of the Special Forces Desperadoes of WWII by Damien Lewis, the film
portrays a heavily fictionalised version of the role played by Winston Churchill's Special Operations Executive in Operation Postmaster.
The Ministry of Ungentlemanly Warfare had its premiere on April 13, 2024, in New
York, and was released in the United States on April 19, 2024.
The film explores themes of army, operation, based
on novel or book, spy, world war ii.
The tone is lighthearted.